(Leonard:)I'll send them a basket of muffins.
(Howard:)Now, inside we've got motion detectors,
infrared sensors...
(Howard:)...and cameras connected to a server...
(Howard:)...running state-of-the-art
facial-recognition software.
(Leonard:)Where did you get all this stuff?
(Howard:)I got a buddy over at
the Department of Defense.
(Leonard:)-He just gave it to you?
-I'm sure he would've if I'd asked.
(Howard:)Ironically, their security isn't
all that good.
(Penny(entering):)Raj, your car is blocking me.
[ALARM WAILING]
VOICE:
Intruder alert. Intruder alert.
(Penny(entering):)-Intruder alert.
-What the hell?
(Leonard:)-Sorry, let me help you.
-Intruder alert.
(Sheldon:)Wonderful security system if
we're attacked by a school of tuna.
(Man on TV:)Don't worry,
the net's gonna be electrified.
(Howard:)Picture her on the floor,
spasming uncontrollably.
(Sheldon:)Better.
SHELDON [IN VOICE-OVER]:
Sheldon's journal.
(Sheldon:)Security system in place.
However, sleep continues to elude me.
(Sheldon:)I've seen the underbelly of Pasadena...